locationindependent.com 2016-10-19

# Privacy Policy | Location Independent

This policy (together with our [terms of website use](http://locationindependent.com/terms-of-website-use/) and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which we, sole trader Lea Woodward trading as Location Independent, will process any personal data we collect from you, or which you provide to us, in the course of using our site www.locationindependent.com

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 we are the data controller.

## Your Information

When you use our site, there are a number of ways in which you provide information and other data to us. By using the site, you consent to us processing and collecting this data, on the terms and for the reasons which are explained below.

## How Your Information Is Used

We may use your information to:

  * Send you our newsletters from time to time.
  * Ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * Provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
  * Carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
  * Allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
  * Notify you about changes to our service.

If you do not want us to use your information for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box on the form on which you submit your data. You can also contact us directly by emailing us.

If you do want to receive information from our carefully selected third parties about goods or services that may be of interest to you, please tick the relevant box on the form on which you submit your data.

Please note that if you click on, or follow, any links from our site to external websites, our privacy policy will no longer apply. Please check the privacy policies of any such external site before submitting any personal data, as we cannot accept any responsibility or liability in relation to them.

## Data Storage

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology.

We take your privacy very seriously, and will take all reasonable steps to protect your personal data, but please be aware that any data which you send to our site is sent at your own risk.

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, processed and/or stored at a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). By submitting your personal data, you agree to this. We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

## Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose your personal information to any of our group companies (which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 736 of the UK Companies Act 1985) and also to third parties in the following circumstances:  –

  * to any prospective seller or buyer of all (or part of) our business or assets;
  * If we are required to do so by law, any applicable regulation or to protect the rights, property, or safety of ourselves or others.
  * This may include disclosing to other companies and organisations in connection with fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Access to Information

You have the right under the Data Protection Act to access the information which we hold about you. If you wish to exercise this right, please send your request to hq@inspiringventures.com. In order to meet our costs in responding, we will charge you a fee of £10.
